我说了对不起 我不太舒服
I said I'm sorry, I'm just not feeling too hot
只是流鼻涕 在电影院也可以流
You're sneezing. You can do that in a movie theatre.
我会瘫倒在电影院的椅子上 累死了
It'll be a nice soft chair when I collapsed./I'm ** babe
别这样 我们要迟到了
oh,come on! We're gonna be late!
第四部从来没公映过
Episode four never/comes to the big screen.
是原汁原味的卢卡斯早期版本
This is the pre-lucas-ized/version,remember?
这个版本先开枪的不是狗脸怪
None of that greedo shooting first crap.
你自己去吧
Go without me
你说什么呢 你不是喜欢星球大战吗
What are you talking about?/You love Star Wars
不喜欢?
Don't you
Ben
什么时候不喜欢的?
Since when?
从一开始我就是假装喜欢
Since just before I pretending I loved it
对不起 我只是好意
I'm sorry. I'm just trying to be supportive.
好吧 我自己去
Fine. I'll go alone.
亲爱的 对不起
Baby I'm sorry.
我也是 我头晕晕的 没法思考
Me too. I'm so woozy. I can hardly think.
我们回家
We're hanging at home
你去看吧
You should go
你感觉到了吗?
Did you just feel something?
感觉? 什么？
Feel? Like what?
有地震?
Is there earthquake?
新泽西有地震?
In New Jersey?
- 天哪/- 怎么了?
- Oh god/-What?
我产生幻觉了
I think I'm like hallucinating.
打911
Call 911
26岁女性 瓦斯管爆炸/她在瓦砾下被埋了6小时
26 years old female, ** exploded under her building. She was pulled out of the rubble after six hours.
两次手术 多处骨折和烧伤
Two surgeries for multiple fractures and burns.
我认为骨折是对建筑物倒塌的正常反应
I'm thinking the broken bones are a/response to the building falling on her head.
还有发烧
And the fever?
所有的遇难者中只有她...
She's the only collapse/victim whose body temperature--
用退烧药
put her on antipyrectics.
已经用了 体温保持在104度(40度)
Already have. The/fever is holding at 104.
意识时有时无
Fluctuating consciousness.
我不能接 我没有团队
I can't take the case./I don't have a team.
- 那就雇一个团队/- 要团队做什么? 我没病人
- So hire a team./- What for?I don't have a case.
有没有面试过谁?
Have you even interviewed anybody?
买车之前先要试驾
You test drive a car before you buy it.
结婚之前还要上床呢/我不会凭10分钟的面试就雇佣某人
You have sex before you get married,I can't/hire a team based on a ten-minute interview.
性生活不和谐怎么办
What if I don't like/having sex with them?
过去两周你无所事事
You've spent the last two/weeks doing absolutely nothing.
音乐会结束
Concert is over.
你什么星球来的/居然能无视范·海伦的
In what twisted universe does/mastering eddie van halen's
华丽的双手琶音指法
two-handed arpeggio technique/count as absolutely nothing?
接下这个病例 否则下个月/你会被调去给这拨病人换绷带
Take the case or you will spend the next month/helping the collapse team change bandages.
我独自给她诊断
I diagnose her. Alone.
一天之内解决 你一周不准烦我
By the end of the day,you/go away for a week.
好
Done.
这样不行的
It's not gonna work.
如果他能解决 就救了女孩一命
If he solves the case,we cure the girl.
证明他不需要团队
And prove he doesn't need a team.
他没法解决的 没那么快
He's not gonna solve/the case. Not that fast.
- 为什么/- 因为他需要团队
- Why not./- Because he needs a team!
- 这只能证明他需要.../- 你想改变他的主意
- And this'll prove to him- - you/wanna change his mind about something,
需要比这个更强的论据
you need a more convincing/argument than you promised.
高热
Fever.
对退烧药和抗生素无反应
Non-responsive to/antibiotics and antipyretics.
意识模糊
Fluctuating consciousness.
开始
Go!
你跟我说话?
you talking to me?
是的
Yes.
想像一下储物间的房顶坍塌
Imagine that the roof/of the storage closet
砸在你最爱的地板打磨机上
collapses on your favorite floor buffer.
然后打磨机开始发热
Which then starts overheating.
为什么我会最爱地板打磨机
Why would I have a/favorite floor buffer?
好吧
Okay.
也许坍塌导致电线短路
Maybe the electrical works got banged/up in there from stuff falling on it.
嗯 有意思
Hmm,interesting.
脑损伤导致体温调节中枢紊乱
Brain damage leading to/hypothalamic dysregulation.
不是
Nah.
如果你是从瓦砾下被拖出来/肯定上过MRI了
If you're brought in covered in/rubble,it's all about the mri'S.
一定会发现的 继续!
We'd have seen that. Come on!
想要赢得游戏 就要努力啊
You gotta earn that fiver.
或者是破洞里掉下来的东西
Or stuff leaked in the/holes,messing it up.
多处开放伤形成感染通路
Lacerations leave multiple/portals for infection.
细菌会对抗生素有反应
Bacterial would have/responded to the antibiotics.
病毒又不会这么高热
Too high for viral.
寄生虫和真菌有可能
Parasites or fungus is possible.
也许是狼疮
Or maybe lupus.
我祖母有狼疮
My grandma has lupus.
对了 自体免疫 我做个狼疮检查
Okay,autoimmune. I'll run a lupus panel.
感染最符合
Infection fits best.
有完整病史就好了
Complete history would be helpful.
到了最讨厌的部分
Which leads to the/worst part of the job.
应付地板打磨机的家人
Dealing with the floor buffer's family.
我们每隔几周说说话/但Ben应该都知道
We talked every couple of weeks,but/ben would know better than I--
没去过野地 没去过任何不寻常的地方
no farms,no travel anywhere weird.
记下来了吗? 打磨机医生
You get that,dr.Buffer?
没有旅行 没有去过农田
No travel,no farm.
档案说她在坍塌之前已经病了
The file says she was sick/before the building collapsed.
我想是感冒
I figured it was just a cold.
你认为有关?
Why,do you think's related?
她之前和现在的病情
Her being sick and her being sick?
通常有关
Often is.
找到她的时候 她已经昏迷
She was unconscious when I found her.
我们有吵架
We'd been fighting.
我想去...
I just want to.
告诉我 她会好起来
just tell me she's gonna be okay.
你会不会好 我都不敢肯定
I'm not even sure you're gonna be okay.
我们会治好她
We're gonna make her all better.
显摆
Showoff.
你应该对人好一点
You oughta be nicer to people.
我们去哪里?
Where are we going?
你知道吗 小孩的嘲笑是会传染的
You know how the laughter of/little children is infectious?
寄生虫和真菌传染性更强
Well,parasites and/fungi are even more so.
要找出是哪一样造成她的大脑出问题
We're gonna find out which one/is making her brain bubble over.
到废墟里?
Where,the building?
现场的救援队说问题不在那儿
Epa's doing that job for/us. They say it's clean.
也就是说我们要向黑莓城堡进发
Which means we're making a/pilgrimage to castle blackberry.
她的名字叫Bradbury
Her name's bradbury.
- 跟他们家要钥匙/- 用不着
- I should ask them for keys./- No need.
找块石头很简单
I'm sure we can find/a large rock somewhere.
我不会破门进入别人家中
I'm not breaking in to somebody's house.
我有原则的
I got principles.
我兜里的几个零钱说你会去的
I got some loose change/here says you don't.
我不干
I'm not doing this.
少于50块不干
For less than a 50.
餐馆在哪?
Where's the restaurant?
什么餐馆?
What restaurant?
你说要带我去吃饭的那家
The one you said you were/taking me to for lunch.
噢 是私家菜
Oh,uh,this one's homier.
冷匹萨归我
Dibs on the cold pizza.
在yutube网站上 看人撬门不吃力
I'm sure it looked easier on youtube.
说什么不需要团队
Yeah,you don't need a team.
没有人陪你 你连束手就擒都做不到
You can't even get/arrested without company.
你是对的 只有一个办法
You're right. Only one solution.
永远不要换掉他们
Never replace them. Ever.
你需要帮助吗
Do you need help?
真行 跟瘸子说便宜话
Yeah,yeah,patronize the poor cripple.
- 让我来/- 好了
- Let me get that./- I got it.
能不能
Will/you--let me
让我来取
just let me get it.
我去检查卧室
I'll check the bedroom.
窗户上有些奇怪的霉菌
Some interesting mold/on the windowsill here!
可能要一段时间
It's gonna take me a while.
我去查浴室
I'll cover the bathroom.
她有本秘密日记
She had a secret diary.
日记还有不秘密的吗?
Is there any other kind?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
洗涤用品促销
There's a sale on liquid tide.
如果你破产了/我可以把我欠你的钱借你一些
If you're broke,I can lend you a/tiny bit of the money I owe you.
不 我不会让你流落到那一步
No,no,I wouldn't put/you in that position.
日记怎么说
What does the diary say?
基本上是她的艳遇列表
It's basically a list/of her sexual encounters.
男的 女的 震动器械
Boys,girls,vibrating appliances.
如果真有 你早大肆引用/不会这么概括
If it was,you'd be/quoting,not summarizing.
日记里全是凄凄惨惨
This is a parade of sad banalities.
我几乎没法起床
I can hardly get out of bed.
觉得很沮丧
Feeling blue.
然后 三个月前/变成了快乐的陈词滥调大游行
Then,three months ago,turns into/a parade of happy banalities.
开始转向了
Starting to turn the corner.
工作有起色了
Job's looking up.
我们可以不用采样了
We can stop swabbing.
她的陈词滥调正变得健康起来
Her clichés are getting healthier.
或者她不那么抑郁了
Or she's less depressed.
难道没有什么药的作用吗?
Aren't there pills that do that?
抗抑郁药不会引起高烧
Antidepressants don't cause fever.
单独不会
Not on their own.
但是急诊室不知道她在吃抗抑郁药
But the E.R. Didn't know/she was on M.A.O.Inhibitors,
所以给她用德美罗(止痛药)
so they gave her demerol.
是个糟糕的组合
It's a nasty combo.
你要做得就是让那男生相信/他的女朋友有个秘密医生
So all you have to do is convince this kid/that his girlfriend had a secret doctor,
藏了一些药 还有一种不为人知的生活
and a secret stash,and a secret life.
好久没有病人朝你挥拳头了/我能旁观吗?
It's been a while since a patient/took a swing at you. Can I watch?
我只要说服妈妈就行了
I only have to convince the mother.
事实上
Actually.
我谁都不用说服
I don't have to convince anyone.
这不可能
This it total crap.
如果她去看精神科医生 我会知道的
If she was seeing a/psychiatrist,I'd know.
如果她在服药 我也会知道的
If she was on drugs,I'd know.
Bradbury太太 请签了协议/我们就开始透析治疗
Mrs.Bradbury,please sign the/form so we can start the dialysis.
为什么吃抗抑郁药?/我不明白!
But why antidepressants?/I don't understand!
Bradbury太太 请签了协议/我们就开始透析治疗
Mrs.Bradbury,please sign the/forms so we can start the dialysis.
别说了
Stop saying that.
Buffer医生 到底怎么回事?/为什么你不告诉我们?
Dr.Buffer,what is going on?/What aren't you telling us?
他是个清洁工?
He's a janitor?
显然更是个多嘴的人
More significantly,a blabbermouth.
House 闭嘴!
House,shut up!
我对House医生的处理方式 感到非常抱歉
I am very sorry how/dr.House handled this.
这是不可原谅的
It is completely unforgivable.
但是他可能是对的
Except if he's right.
透析会过滤她的血液
Dialysis will filter her blood.
没什么可过滤的
There's nothing to filter.
救她的命
Save her life.
她没有抑郁症
She wasn't depressed.
我在Ben身边很痛苦
I'm miserable around ben.
不是我 我喜欢Ben
Not me. I like ben.
2月12号
February 12th.
她要不是很抑郁 就是认为你是个混蛋
Either she's depressed,or/she just thinks you're a jerk.
两者都意味着/你不该是那个决定她治疗方案的人
Neither suggests that you should be/the one directing her medical treatment.
日记里说我女儿在服药吗?
Does the diary say my/daughter's taking these drugs?
- 没有 但从医学上-/- 你在她家里找到药了吗?
- No,but medically- - did/you find drugs in their home?
她也许把药藏在钱包里
She's probably hiding them in her purse.
去上千吨的废墟下面/翻看女士包包太不礼貌了
I thought it would be rude to go/searching under 1,000 tons of rubble.
这是数月前的 那时我们不合
This was months ago. We were in a fight.
这不意味着她抑郁 也不说明她不爱我
It doesn't mean she's depressed. And/it doesn't mean she doesn't love me.
好吧 也许这日记什么也不能证明
Fine,maybe the diary proves nothing.
从另外一方面来讲/全国一半的人都在服抗抑郁药
On the other hand,half the/country's on antidepressants.
而且她的症状与此完美吻合
And it fits her symptoms perfectly.
你女儿还没带婚戒 因此你做决定
No ring on your daughter's finger/means you make the decisions.
现在我不敢确定我是否足够了解她
I'm not sure that I know/her well enough anymore.
你真打算凭他有多了解你女儿/去赌她的命?
You really wanna risk her/life on how well he knows her?
你的吉他在我手里/别告诉任何人 等我的指示
I have your guita tell no/one await my in structions
Wilson 你个笨蛋
Wilson,you idiot.
听仔细了 没人会受伤
listen carefully,and/no one will get hurt.
你必须遵从指示
You must follow these instructions.
如果试图联络联邦调查局
Any attempt to contact the F.B.I.
或其他执法部门 或Cuddy
Or other law enforcement/agencies or. cutty.
将会导致
will be met with.
要大杯可乐 不加冰
And a large coke. No ice.
还给我
Give it back.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
是不是有人绑架了你的吉他?
Did someone. kidnap your guitar?
价值12,000美金1967年版飞V形吉他?/或别的什么?
A $12,000 1967 flying v? Or something?
你把它藏哪儿了?
Where'd you hide it?
你把我想得这么勇敢聪明/我真是受宠若惊
I'm flattered you would consider/me this bold and brilliant.
不 因为那需要--
No,'cause it/takes a cri--
罪犯极大的才智从大厅里一个没有上锁
it takes a criminal mastermind to/pull off a heist from an unlocked,
没有把守的房间偷窃
unguarded room down the hall.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我? 什么都不要
Me? Nothing.
但我肯定绑架者肯定有所要求
But I'm sure the kidnapper/wants what every kidnapper wants.
你得面试5到7个符合要求的应聘者
To see you interview five to seven/well-qualified fellowship candidates.
我不需要团队
I don't need a team.
你对着清洁工试探意见
You were bouncing ideas off a janitor.
解决了病例!
And solved the case!
Hi.
我是Cuddy医生
I'm dr.Cuddy.
能听见我说什么的话 眨一下眼
If you can hear what/I'm saying,blink once.
你现在不能说话 喉咙里有根管子
You can't talk right now. You/have a tube down your throat.
别动你的头
And try not to move your head.
你经历了一场可怕的意外
You've been in a terrible accident.
但没有什么永久性损伤
But it looks like you will/have no permanent injuries.
高烧一度很厉害 但现在退了
You've had a bad/fever,but it's gone now.
我一直在这儿 亲爱的 好吗?/我不会离开的
I've been here the whole/time,honey,okay? I'm not leaving.
这很重要
This is very important.
我需要你 是就眨一下眼 不就眨两下
I need you to blink one/for yes,twice for no.
你是不是看过精神科医生?
Were you seeing a psychiatrist?
你是不是在服单氨氧化酶抑制剂?/抗抑郁药
Were you on m.A.O.Inhibitors?/The antidepressant.
Megan 没事的 我爱你
Megan,it's okay. It doesn't/matter,okay?I love you.
亲爱的? 亲爱的 出什么事了?
Honey? Honey,what's wrong?
Megan 你还好吗?
Megan,are you all right?
发生什么事了? 我们让她心烦了?
What's happening? Are we upsetting her?
心跳太快了
Heart is beating too fast.
- 让家属出去/- Megan?
- Get the family out of here./- Megan?
- Megan?/- 充电到200.
- Megan?/- Charging to 200.
- Meg,meg./- Megan.
完毕!
Clear!
我们电击她回到窦性心律/但还是心动过速
we shocked her back into sinus/rhythm,but she's still tachycardic.
吸引人
Fascinating.
同样教人好奇的是
Equally fascinating is.
你为什么到这儿来?
why are you here?
你要是赢了那个赌 我不会打扰你
I was gonna leave you/alone if you won the bet.
但你输了
But you lost.
我解释了发烧
I explained the fever.
我们讨论的就只有发烧
Which is all we were talking about.
她确认了抗抑郁药
She confirmed the antidepressants.
如果想解释心脏问题去和别人打赌吧
Go bet with someone else if you/want to explain the heart problems.
她是靠眨眼确认的
She confirmed them by winking.
也许是对某个可爱的家伙眨眼/(照片: 我还活着)
Maybe there was a cute/guy across the room.
我治疗的时候她好多了
She got better when I treated her.
尽管我不可爱
Even I'm not that cute.
两个无关的症状也许不过是巧合
Two unrelated/symptoms,just a coincidence.
或是你抓着救命稻草/不想承认你不能独自解决这问题
Or you're grasping at straws to avoid/admitting you can't do this on your own.
好吧 什么能解释发烧和持续的心动过速?
Fine,what explains the fever/and persistent tachycardia?
可以是任何病 心内膜炎
Could be anything. Endocarditis.
不是 发烧 没有感染
Nope. Fever,no infection.
继续 你做得很好
keep going,you're doing great.
你赢了
You win.
- 我不相信你/- 我不玩这游戏
- I don't believe you./- I'm not gonna play this game.
给我那些该死的简历
Just give me the damn resumes.
和我的吉他
And my guitar.
不在我这儿
I don't have it.
不过我确实听到过一些
Although I did hear some.
轰鸣的弹奏声从那沙发下面传来
plangent strumming from/under that couch earlier.
这个绑匪不只大胆 简直邪恶
This kidnapper isn't/just bold,he's diabolical.
我猜他发觉不应该把吉他还给你
I guess he realized he probably/shouldn't give it back to you
直到你面试结束
until after you've had the interviews.
你什么也没写
Huh,you didn't write anything.
所以说 你没找到那个唯一的圆满答案
So what you're saying is,you didn't/find that one big explanation.
因为根本没有
cause there isn't one.
聪明
Clever.
就算是
Well,let's just say.
你的抗抑郁理论能解释发烧
your antidepressant theory/does explain the fever.
那心脏呢? 别说因为被楼压的
What about the heart? And don't say a building fell on her.
好吧
Okay.
- 一个建筑倒塌/- 闭嘴
- A structure collapsed./- Shut up
别这么说 这符合
come on,it fits.
被挤压的肌肉组织释放钾 导致室颤
Hed musculature releases/potassium,causes v-tac.
事故发生后她就该有症状 而不是两天后
you'd think shd syndrome after/she was crushed,not two days later.
微脉管堵塞
Microvascular occlusions.
血液需要那么长时间重新灌流
Takes that long for/the blood to reperfuse.
她的心脏膨胀了
She'd have a baggy heart.
回声测定确认
Echo it to confirm.
挤压症状是好是坏?
Is crush syndrome good or bad?
听起来像好的吗?
Does it sound good?
我是说 比起其他的可能
I mean,compared to the/other things it could be.
没有其它的可能性
There are no other things it could be.
那为什么我们还有给她做检查?
Then why are you testing her?
好问题
Excellent question.
什么 那是什么?
What. what is it?
心脏没问题
The heart's fine.
她为什么在出汗?
Why is she sweating?
她又发烧了
Her fever's back.
为什么她又发烧了?
Why would her fever be back?
我不能说
I can't say.
你不知道?
You don't know?
我知道 我就是不能说
I know,I just can't say.
因为你会打我
'Cause you'll hit me.
咱们找个证人 再讨论吧
Let's discuss this/in front of witnesses.
DT's ?/(震颤性谵妄 嗜酒)
The dt's?
那么 她现在又成了酗酒者了?
So she's an alcoholic now?
她第一次发烧是由抗抑郁药引起的
Her first fever was from the/medication for her depression.
或者 你错了
Or you're wrong.
第二发热 是由于她为了抗抑郁/而自我麻醉
The second fever was from the/self-medication for depression.
你疯了
This is insane.
你觉得 如果她不断喝醉/我会不知道?
You don'think i would have/noticed her being constantly drunk?
你基本上是和Sylvia Plath生活在一起/(美国诗人 严重抑郁患者)
You were practically/living with sylvia plath.
你没注意到
You didn't notice that.
注意语气/要不 我会打你的
Tone it down or I will hit you.
好吧 我做个肝酶检测
Fine,I'll do liver enzyme tests.
肌肉骨骼外伤也能导致肝酶上升
lir zymes can also be elevated/from musculoskeletal trauma.
不管她是不是酗酒 都会异常
They'd be there whether she had/a drinking problem or not.
他们不知道
They don't know that.
就假装确诊一下
Just pretend to confirm.
怎么治疗?
What's the treatment?
她不是酗酒者
She's not an alcoholic.
用酒解宿醉 静脉注射酒精
Hair of the dog,iv alcohol.
几天之后逐渐减量
Taper it off after a few days.
她病着 受了伤 半死了
She's sick and/traumatized and half-dead.
你还想让她喝醉
You wanna make her drunk.
就这么做吧
Just do it.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
我们住在一起/想要生孩子
We lived together,we/were gonna have kids.
你都不怎么了解她
You barely even know her.
很明显 你也不了解
Apparently,neither did you.
你好
Hello?
你好 我找Trevor Kaufman
Hi,could I speak to trevor.kaufman?
嗨 这是Trev 什么事儿?
Yo yo,it's trev. What up?
这是Gregory House医生
This is dr.Gregory house.
你明天能来面试吗?
Can you come in tomorrow to interview?
House? 真的吗? 太棒了!
House? Are you serious?Awesome!
嗨 哥们儿 House要给我面试!
Hey,dude,I got the house interview!
哦 看着我!
oh,look at me!
House要给我面试!
I got the house interview!
哥们儿 闭嘴 我还在打电话!
dude,shut up! I'm on the phone!
- 闭嘴!/- 我多棒啊!
- Shut up!/- I'm so cool!
把电话还给我/把电话还给我!
Give me the phone back./Give me the phone back!
有人传呼我
I got a page.
没有
No,you didn'T.
说是紧急情况
They called a code.
没有
No,they didn'T.
你有个传呼 但不是我们呼的
You got a page,but not from us.
你看没看过 火狐一号出击 这个电影?
Did you ever see raid on entebbe?
看过 到最后 他们释放了人质
Yeah,in the end,they/release the hostages.
你觉得那个怎么样?
How's that working for you?
乌干达人挺公平的
The ugandans played fair.
他们没有在以色列人到达之前转移人质
They didn't move the/hostages on the israelis.
我又一次为绑架者的出色策略折服
Once again,I am in awe of the/kidnapper's tactical brilliance.
什么是 el fuego del amor(爱火)/你为什么需要十个?
What is el fuego del amor and/why do you need ten of them?
是电视剧
It's a telanovela.
我在学西班牙语
I'm learning spanish.
说 "再见"
Say adios.
你是不是在删我的录影?
Are you erasing my tivo?
House 不要删那季最后一集
House,not the season finale.
我不和恐怖分子谈判
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
我要把他们赶出藏身之处
I smoke them out of their hidey-holes.
你知道 如果你不谈判/恐怖分子会怎么做吗?
Do you know what terrorists/do when you don't negotiate?
他们会搞恐怖活动
They terrorize.
放马过来
Bring it on.
体温降下来了
Fever's down.
出汗少了/心脏工作正常
Sweating has abated./Heart's working fine.
我猜House是对的 再一次
I guess house was right. Again.
是好消息 对吧?
That's good news,right?
是好消息
It is good news.
这说明什么/她酗酒?
So what does this/mean,she's an alcoholic?
没有其它解释?
There's no other explanation?
没有 对不起
No,sorry.
我不明白
It doesn't make any sense.
Cuddy医生 她的嘴又这样了
Dr.Cuddy. she's doing this/thing with her mouth again.
过去的几个小时里 来来回回 好几次了
It's been on and off for/the last couple hours.
她是不是要说话?
Is she trying to talk?
不是
no.
我觉得她是在尖叫
I think she's screaming.
早
Morning!
你从哪儿来?
Where did you come from?
从猿人进化而来/如果你相信民主党
Apes,if you believe the democrats.
我听说 你见证了我又一次正确的判断
I heard you were there/when I was proven right.
酒精疗法治愈了心脏和发热的问题
The alcohol treatment took away/the heart and fever problems.
没错 我也见证了 你被证明是错的
Yes,I was also there when/you were proven wrong.
她无声地叫了两个小时
She'd been silently/screaming for two hours.
淀粉酶和脂肪酶证明了
Amylase and lipase are through the roof.
她有胰腺炎
She has pancreatitis.
静脉注射酒精可以导致胰腺炎
Iv alcohol can cause pancreatitis.
好吧
Okay.
- 你不打算跟我争论一下?/- 没
- You're not gonna argue with me?/- Nope.
- 你觉得我是对的?/- 不
- You think I'm right?/- Nope.
- 为什么不争论?/- 不
- Why not?/- Nope.
这不是个 对 或 不对 的问题
It's not really a yes or no question.
这就是为什么我不回答
Which is why i'm not answering it.
- 如果不是静脉注射酒精的问题 那就是/- 没兴趣
- If it's not the iv alcohol,it's/gotta be- - not interested.
如果我错了 她就会死了
If I'm wrong,she's gonna die.
你确定你还是医学院院长吗
Are you sure you're/still dean of medicine.
我没兴趣跟你争论 是因为/我没有兴趣捧你
I'm not interested in arguing because/I'm not interested in enabling you.
你需要别人 检测你的观点
You need someone to bounce ideas off of.
你需要一个团队
You need a team.
别跟着我
Don't follow me.
M.A.O(单胺氧化酶)抑制剂造成发热
M.A.O.Inhibitor caused the fever.
酒精造成胰腺炎
Alcohol caused the pancreatitis.
停用酒精造成室颤
Alcohol withdrawal/caused the v-tach. Le."
你的推理无懈可击
Your logic is irrefutable.
你错了
you're wrong.
哦 你会相信谁?
Well,who are you gonna believe?
一个经典玩具/还是一个没信心的女人
A classic toy or a woman who,
但凡对自己有点信心
if she had any confidence in her ideas,
都不需要用水袋胸罩来转移注意力
wouldn't feel the need to/distract you with a water bra?
你真的要治疗胰腺炎吗?
Are you really just gonna/treat the pancreatitis?
你是来给我撑腰的吗?
Are you here to enable me?
我不想让她死于你的顽固
I don't want her to die/because you're stubborn.
哇 你可以既鼓励又理性
Wow,so you can enable and/rationalize at the same time.
看来你仍是医学院的院长
Guess you are still dean of medicine.
如果你是对的/那好端端一个姑娘
If you're right,then this guy,
不是工作狂 不是反社会者
who's not an ass,who's not a/workaholic,who's not a sociopath,
却不知什么原因吃起抗抑郁药 还酗酒
has somehow missed both her/depression and severe alcoholism.
是一对保有秘密的恋人
Yes,imagine that,a couple with secrets.
她为什么要撒谎?
Why would she lie?
好吧 酗酒 可能不想大肆宣扬
Okay,alcoholism you/don't wanna advertise.
但是...
But...
如果你是对的 胰腺肯定有问题
if you're right,there'd be an/abnormality on the pancreas.
最少做个核磁确诊一下
At least do an mri to confirm.
哦 我的天
Oh,my god.
这个人是来真的啊
This guy means business.
或者是一群人 可能是团伙
Or guys.Could be multiple guys.
或者是个姑娘 谁知道?
Or a gal.Who knows?
我只能说他够狠的
All I can say is,this reeks of boldness.
我不要雇一个团队
I am not hiring a team.
你有没有 慢慢的给吉他紧过弦?
You ever tighten a guitar/string really,really slowly?
当琴弦超过所能承受的张力
Past the point it can handle the strain?
会发出那种奇怪的声音
It makes this weird sound.
就像是尖叫
Almost like a scream.
我以为会很有趣
I thought this was gonna be fun.
你搞我 我搞你
I messed with you,you messed with me.
最后 你会投降
Eventually,you give in.
但 你这么没有幽默感 让我很惊讶
But you've shown a/startling lack of humor,
让我开始思考
which got me thinking.
哦 天啊
Oh,god.
你不想雇一个团队的原因/到底是什么?
What's the real reason/you won't hire a team?
我说了 我不需要团队
I told you,I don't need a team.
那么雇三个人 让他们干坐着好了
Then hire three people and/let 'em sit on their asses.
这样不好
That wouldn't be right.
三年前 你雇了一个团队/什么改变了呢?
Three years ago,you hired/a team.What's changed?
我变成了一个有原则的人
I have become a man of principle.
我变聪明了
I've gotten smarter.
到底怎么说才能让"苏格拉底"闭嘴呢?
What answer will make socrates shut up?
变化就是 你雇了一个团队/你和团队紧密相连
What's changed is,you/connected with a team.
和团队一起工作
You worked with a team.
却失去了这个团队
And you lost a team.
妈的
Damn.
她的胰腺没有异常
There's no abnormalities/in her pancreas.
你坠入爱河 结了婚
You fall in love,you get married.
有一半机会 你会惨淡收场
50% chance it'll end in misery.
雇佣下属则更难
Hiring employees can be even tougher.
因为你知道 他们终究是要离开的
Because you/know,eventually,they're gonna leave.
她的肝包膜处 有个T2强信号
There's increased t2 signal/on her hepatic capsule.
你若懂我意思的话
If you know what I mean.
你受伤了
You got hurt.
别伤心了
Get over it.
现在 不介意的话
Now,if you'll excuse me,
我的病人的嘴巴和肛门快要出血了
my patient is about to start/bleeding out of her mouth and anus.
内出血
Internal bleeding.
不再是了
Not anymore.
现在到处是血
Now it's all over the place.
你来这干嘛?
Why are you here?
下面可是我的病人啊
That's my patient down there.
你来这儿是因为我在这儿
You're here because I'm here.
我不会再纵容你了
I am done enabling you.
我知道
I know.
酒精没有导致胰腺炎/内出血导致了胰腺炎
The alcohol didn't cause the/pancreatitis,the internal bleeding did.
问题是 什么导致了内出血?
The question is,what caused/the internal bleeding?
我好恨我自己啊
I hate myself.
你确实知道/一栋大楼倒在病人身上了
You do know that the patient/had a building land on her.
那是四天前
Four days ago.
出血可能始于任何时候
Bleeding can start at any time.
有五个地方出血
It's bleeding from five different sites.
你觉得他们对好了表 同时发作?
You think they/synchronized their watches?
在整臀手术之后 她服了杀鼠灵
She got warfarin after her hip surgery.
明摆着是要出血的嘛
It's designed to mess/with bleeding patterns.
发烧 心脏问题 出血
Fever,heart,and bleeding.
三个问题 三种完全不同的解释
Three problems,three completely/different explanations.
她一定是世上最倒霉的女人了
She must be the unluckiest/woman in the world.
我之所以坚持这个疯狂的想法
I only cling to this crazy theory
是因为每一步都证明是正确的
because it's been proven/right every step of the way.
每一步治疗都有效
Each treatment worked.
是啊 她看上去真健康
Yes,she looks perfectly healthy.
出血是其他病因的症状
This much bleeding is a/symptom of something more.
你需要一个团队
And you need a team
因为你错了 你会害死这个女人的
because you're wrong and/you're gonna kill this woman.
如果我有团队 这个病人早就死了
If I had a team,this/patient would be dead.
因为他们会替我留守在此
Because they'd be here instead of me
他们不会注意到这个女人子宫的大小
and they wouldn't notice the/size of this woman's uterus.
嗨! 进行得如何?
Hi!How's it going?
我来观察一下 不介意吧?
Mind if I observe?
在上面安个大窗户 用意在此啊
Got a big room up top/window just for that.
哦 停手
Oh,stop that.
你想要观察阴道 网上有
You wanna look at vaginas,there/are websites for that.
你觉得我钱太多了?
Think I'm made of money?
你能把他弄走吗?
Can you get him out of here?
扩大的子宫
Enlarged uterus.
说明她最近怀过孕
Means that she was recently pregnant.
她是个谎话精/但也不可能背着男友藏着孩子
She's a good liar,but I doubt she/could hide a baby from her boyfriend.
子宫刮痕说明她曾堕过胎
Scraping in the uterus indicates/that she had an abortion.
但是病史没写
But nothing in her medical history.
隐瞒堕胎的原因只有一个
Only one reason to hide an abortion.
男友想要孩子 但她不想
Boyfriend wants babies,she doesn'T.
她到处流血
She's bleeding everywhere.
除非那人是拿了把枪堕的胎...
Unless the guy was performing/an abortion with a shotgun...
别怂恿他!
stop enabling him!
不是堕胎的关系 而是堕胎后的事情
It's not the abortion,it's/what she did after.
男友会留意避孕套
The boyfriend would/have noticed condoms.
他会留意她的节欲
He would notice abstinence.
但他没法留意避孕药
He would not notice the pill.
瞧 我不需要团队!
Which means,I don't need a team!
嘿 你那位未来岳母大人呢?
Hey,where's your/mother-in-common-law?
House医生 这位是Doug Mcmurtry
Dr.House,this is doug mcmurtry.
她的女友曾和Megan一起工作...
His girlfriend was/working with megan when...
她死了?
she's dead?
今天早上去世的
She passed this morning.
那你为啥还在这儿呢?
Well,then why are you still here?
我需要老太太的同意/来做一些治疗
I need the old lady's/consent to do some treatment.
你有什么发现?
What'd you find out?
我很想告诉你/但你既然不是法定亲属...
I wish I could tell you,but since/you're not legally related...
你到底发现了什么?
What the hell did you find out?
你的女友堕过胎
Your girlfriend had an abortion.
明白我为什么不想说了吧?
See why I didn't tell you?
我也不该告诉你 她一直在服避孕药
I'd be insane to also tell/you that she's on the pill.
不 她没有
No,she's not.
如果他们知道她在用药
If they'd known she was on it,
他们也不会在她整臀手术之后/给她血液稀释剂
they wouldn't have given her a/blood thinner after her hip surgery.
这些综合起来导致了出血
The combination caused the bleeding.
这是好消息 是可治愈的
It's good news.It's treatable.
给她它莫西芬就行了/(一种抗雌激素)
Just give her tamoxifen.
- 通常用于乳癌/- 这不是真的
- Which is normally a breast cancer/- it's not true.
因为 我们想要孩子
'Cause,uh,we wanna have kids.
嗯
Huh.
我已经验了血
See,I already did the blood tests.
所以 要么是她对你撒谎/要么是验血结果对我们撒谎
And either she lied to/you,or her blood lied to us.
转告Megan 她能康复 我很开心
Tell megan I'm glad she's gonna be okay.
你好吗?
How are you doing?
我得了癌症
I got cancer.
你在肿瘤病房
You're on an oncology ward.
这儿 人人有癌症
Everybody's got cancer.
你想要人同情/你想试试"地球依旧转动"的感觉
You want sympathy,you wanna try the/"hardly anything wrong with the wold
为何不让我现在就带你去呢?
in fact,why don't i/take you there right now?
你的病有多重? 能走路吗?
How sick are you?Can you walk?
你是医生吗?
Are you a doctor?
今天入院
Admitted today.
五日化疗的第一天
First day of a five day chemo course.
是的 你能走路 来吧 我们走
Yeah,you can walk.Come on,let's go.
Wilson医生知道你在这吗?
Does dr.Wilson know you're here?
他若不知道 这么做就太傻了
Well,if he didn't,this/would be really stupid.
因为那样他就不知道他病人上哪去了
'Cause then he wouldn't/know where his patient was.
他会怀疑病人被绑架了 楼上的房间更大
He might think he no,the/room upstairs is bigger.
还有有线电视/有漂亮护士给洗海绵浴
It's got cable.Better/looking sponge bath nurses.
如果你不舒服 可以直接呼我/别找Wilson医生了
If you feel sick,you call/me directly,not dr.Wilson.
他在接受最后一轮的荷尔蒙注射/(变性手术)
He's getting his last/set of hormone shots.
你给她服它莫西芬?
You put her on tamoxifen?
一种抗癌药?
An anti-cancer drug?
它阻止雌激素吸收
It blocks estrogen receptors.
它是否也抑制呼吸和肾功能?
Does it also block breathing/and kidney function?
她在崩溃
She's crashing.
并不能说明我错了
Doesn't mean I was wrong.
我们这就把他的病人带来 谢谢
We're bringing his/patient over now,thanks.
这里有没有人是医生?
Anybody here a doctor?
肾衰竭 高烧不退 呼吸困难
Kidney failure,spiking/fever,breathing difficulties.
有什么想法没?
Any theories?
我置身在M. Night Shyamalan的电影中吗?/(好莱坞著名印度裔明星)
Am I in an m.Night shyamalan movie?
你是House是吧?
You're house,right?
我想你认识我是因为
Okay,I assume you know me because
我曾经欺负过你 你的病人/或是你的亲人
I once insulted you,your/patient,or your relatives.
如果真是这样 我道歉/我那天喝醉了
If that's so,I apologize.I/was drunk that day.
病人一开始显示挤压外伤
Patient initially presented/with crush injuries.
我认识你/是因为Cuddy医生发了一条备忘录
I know you because/dr.Cuddy issued a memo.
告诉你要全力配合我?
Telling to cooperate fully with me?
不是
Nope.
我就知道这机会太渺茫
I figured that was a long shot.
这里有谁没接到这个备忘录的?
Anybody here not get that memo?
真菌感染
Fungal infection.
你不是有病人吗?
Don't you have a patient?
她摄取甲安菲他明 兴奋过头/朝自己腿上开了一枪
She shot herself in the/leg while high on meth.
让她受受苦也没什么不好
Wouldn't hurt her to be/in pain for a little while.
若是真菌感染/这会儿已经扩散到眼睛了
Fungal infection would/be in her eyes by now.
嗜血杆菌
Haemophylus.
没法解释持续高烧
Doesn't explain the remitting fever.
你听说...我要雇人 是不是?
You've heard...that I've/got a job opening,right?
我只是关心人罢了
I just care about people.
急性呼吸窘迫综合症
Acute respiratory distress syndrome.
A.R.D.S.不能解释任何问题
A.R.D.S.Doesn't explain anything.
只能解释呼吸症状
Except the breathing.
如果你充满爱心 这份工作就没什么戏
If you care about people,you're/not getting the job.
我没说真话 挤压综合症
I was lying.Crush syndrome.
无法解释呼吸症状
Doesn't explain the breathing.
急性呼吸窘迫综合征有什么不妥?
What was the problem with A.R.D.S.?
只能解释呼吸症状
Only explained the breathing.
那挤压综合症呢?
And the crush syndrome?
无法解释呼吸症状
It didn't explain the breathing.
你喜欢说话工工整整的?
You a fan of symmetry?
是啊
Sure.
有点怪
Weird.
因为你的眼睛不太对称
'Cause your eyes are lopsided.
我说的眼睛意思是指胸部
And by eyes,I mean breasts.
A.R.D.S/急性呼吸窘迫综合征
A.R.D.S
还有挤压综合症/都可能由重度创伤导致
And crush syndrome,both/reactions to severe trauma.
她为什么不能两样都得?
Why can't she have both?
因为...
Because...
那样我们就无能为力了
because then there's/nothing we could do.
天 你让我想起了某人
Boy,you remind me of someone.
把你的简历给我
Send me your resume.
放在那堆我不看简历的最上面
I'll put it on top of the pile/that I'm never gonna look at.
我无法离开
I couldn't leave.
你看起来不像那种无法放弃的人
You don't seem like the type of/person who would give up on giving up.
我爱她
I love her.
你喜欢的是
You love somebody.
不沾酒 愿意和你生孩子的人
Someone who didn't drink,who/wanted to have babies.
不是精神痛苦的那种
And wasn't miserable.
我知道她说谎了 但是...
I know she lied,but...
你在做什么?
what are you doing?
为什么要和他说这些
Why are you saying these things to him?
你爱的女人这世上不存在
The woman you love doesn't exist.
这个女人快要死了
This woman is dying.
急性呼吸窘迫综合征/挤压综合症
She has acute respiratory distress/syndrome and crush syndrome.
她的身体基本垮了
Her body's basically giving up.
我们可以给她做透析维持下去/抱最好的希望
We can keep her on supportive/dialysis and hope for the best.
当我没说 手臂上有个肿块
Never mind.She has a lump on her arm.
是不是说你的诊断错了?
Does that mean you're wrong?
错了就是好消息了
That would be good news for you guys.
活检后就知道了
We'll know after the biopsy.
- 这是哪个病人的?/- Megan...
- Which patient is that?/- Megan...
- House的病人/- 是的
- house's patient./- Yep.
没有收到我的通知么?
Didn't you get my memo?
收到了
Sure.
两个都收到了
Got both memos.
两个
Both.
第二个通知说忽略第一个?
And the second memo said/to ignore the first memo?
是的
Yep.
有些奇怪
Seemed odd.
还通知做个核磁共振成像
Did an mri and...
你当然做了
of course you did.
有发现么?
What'd you find?
有点可怕 长满全身了
It's kind of freaky.She's got/growths all over the place.
肿瘤?
She's got tumors?
不完全是
Not exactly.
嗜酸性肉芽肿
The growths are eosinophilic granulomas.
通常是过敏反应引起的
They are usually from/allergic reactions.
我现在要给她用类固醇
I'm putting her on steroids.
对什么过敏? 她没有过敏症
Allergy to what?She/doesn't have allergies.
很难讲
We don't know.
不幸的是 她服用的药物里
Unfortunately,the only/drug she's had enough
只有多头孢菌素产生过敏反应
of to have this kind of/reaction is cephalosporin.
不幸的是?
And why is that unfortunate?
因为她两个月前开始服用的
Because she was on it two months ago.
是你要说的意思么?
That's what you mean,right?
是治疗链球菌性喉炎的/所以她不可能过敏
She took it for strep throat,so/she can't be allergic to it.
表面上是这样
It would seem so.
这医院到底对她做了什么?
What is this hospital doing to her?
她得了三种不同的大病
She has had three/separate medical disasters.
结果因为不可能的过敏 奄奄一息?
And now she's dying of an/allergy she can't possibly have!
Lee先生 我要查一下...
Mr.Lee,I just have to check...
Sam? 你还好吧?
sam?Are you okay?
怎么是你?
What are you doing here?
小憩一会儿
I was taking a nap.
我的病人哪去了?
Where's my patient?
你偷走了我的病人
You stole my patient.
你绑票了我的吉他
You kidnapped my guitar.
把他还给我
Give him back.
只有等你把她还给我
Only when you give her back.
它是女的?
It's a she?
是哦 肯定不是个男的
Well,it's certainly not a dude.
这是个吉他 你偷走的是个人
It's a guitar!You took a human being!
看看谁没有幽默感了?
Now who doesn't have a sense of humor?
我在远程监护这个病人
I'm monitoring the guy remotely.
做什么? 倾听远方传来的尖叫?
What are you,listening for/the distant sound of screaming?
护士会叫我的
The nurses know to call me.
她们还不知道他是谁!
They don't know who he is!
名字病例报告上就写了
His name's right there on the chart.
好了走吧 我在办正事
Now go away.I'm working.
她们要是给错了药
They give him the wrong meds,
天知道会发生什么
who the hell knows what's gonna happen?
House!
坏事难防
Bad things would happen.
他在318病房
He's in room 318.
你要--你要给Megan用什么药?
What are you-- what/are you giving megan?
Megan? 没什么
Megan?Nothing.
没什么? 怎么回事?/她怎么了?
Nothing?What's going/on?What's wrong with her?
她? 没事
Her?Nothing.
那你为什么要给药?
Then why are you giving her drugs?
只是些安非他命 让她醒过来
Just some amphetamines to wake her up.
假设她说谎了 一切都可以得到解释
Everything could be/explained by her lying to you.
那些抗抑郁药 酗酒 避孕药
The antidepressants,the/drinking,the pill.
到目前为止
Until now.
现在她过敏了 而病例报告上却说不会
Now she's allergic to something the/chart says she's not allergic to.
说谎的不是她 而是病例报告
That's not her lying,that's/the chart lying.
这里必有蹊跷
Which doesn't make S.
认识Liz Master么?
Do you know liz masters?
不认识
No.
你在停尸间外碰到过她的男朋友
That was her boyfriend who/you met outside the morgue.
嗯
Mm.
这是她的病例报告
This is her chart.
她在服用MAO抑制剂治疗抑郁
She's on M.A.O.Inhibitors/for depression.
她在用避孕药
She's on the pill.
一个月前堕胎
She had an abortion a month ago.
对头孢菌素过敏
And she's allergic to cephalosporin.
你说的是什么意思?/她不是Megan?
What's going on here?What,are/you saying this isn't megan?
嗯
Yes.
Ben
Ben.
什么时候不喜欢的?
Since when?
从一开始就是假装喜欢
Since right before i began/pretending i loved it.
她的体型 身材 头发颜色都和Megan一样
She's the same size as/megan,same build,same hair color.
她们都受了很重的伤 让人认不出来
They were both horribly/injured.Unrecognizably.
急救小组不会在事故现场再次确认
Emt teams do not second/guess family members'
家属的指认
identifications at accident scenes.
不 Liz昨天死了 她不是Liz
No.Liz died yesterday.This isn't liz.
我认得出Megan
I know megan.
我熟悉她的头发
I know her hair.
她的手
I know her hands.
她的气味 哦
I know her smell.Oh.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
Liz...
哦 上帝!
oh,god!
你的女朋友从未对你说谎
Your girlfriend never lied to you.
都是我一个人完成的 妈咪
I did it all by myself,mommy.
你在和我说话?
You talking to me?
离我远点
Go away.
都是我一个人完成的 妈咪
I did it all by myself,mommy.
你怎么知道是我的?
How'd you know it was me?
有一种受伤的野猫的气息
There's a scent given/off by wounded,feral cats.
你错了
You were wrong.
我都对了
I got everything right.
- 只是治错了人/- 他们的感情很好
- Just treated the wrong/- they had a good relationship.
他都没认出来
He couldn't even identify her.
关于你不需要团队 也是错的
And you were wrong about needing a team.
她差点死去
She almost died.
我差点就需要团队了
So I almost need a team.
你总是一副"世人皆醉你独醒"的架势
You were content with your/"people are idiots" theory.
Cameron就不会轻信
But cameron would/never have accepted that
这个人对他的爱人一无所知
this guy knew nothing/about the love of his life.
当你判断是多种病症并发
And as soon as you claimed/it was multiple conditions
Foreman会尽一切可能证明你错了
foreman would have done/anything to prove you wrong.
Chase会尽一切可能证明你对
And then chase would have done/anything to prove you right.
有他们在 几天前就该解决了
Any one of them would/have solved this days ago.
组织团队
Hire a team.
我不管你怎么做
I don't care how you do it.
只要给我做
Just do it.
有时 我会错
sometimes,I am wrong.
我有观察的天分
I have a gift for observation.
在不同环境下审视人心
For reading people in situations.
但有时候 我会犯错
But sometimes,I am wrong.
这将是你经历最长的一个面试
This will be the longest/job interview of your life.
我会用各种方法 在你们看来
I will test you in ways/that you will often consider
不公平的 苛刻的 违法的办法/来考验你们
unfair,demeaning,and illegal.
而且你们的看法没错
And you will often be right.
看看你左边
Look to your left.
看看你的右边
Now look to your right.
6周以后 你们中有人将会出局
By the end of six weeks,one/of you will be gone.
还有28个人也是这个下场
As will 28 more of you.
准备受死吧
Wear a cup.